Guide to the Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers International Union, Local 3 Records and Photographs WAG.135
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Souvenir Programs, 1930-1993
  This series contains the souvenir programs of a variety of locals and trade organizations. Photographs and laudatory accounts of union history are here in abundance. Of particular interest are programs related to the Cake Shows which picture some fine examples of the output of the skilled bakers.
  - Local 1: 56th Anniversary Celebration Ball and Cake Parade, Mar 14, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Local 1: 57th Anniversary, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Local 1: 1944 Year Book (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Local 1: 1945 Year Book (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Local 1: 1946 Year Book (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Local 1: 62nd Anniversary Celebration, 1948 Year Book (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Local 1: 100th Anniversary, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Local 1: 101st Anniversary, Ball and Cake Show, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Local 1: 103rd Anniversary Annual Dance and Merger Celebration, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Old Local 3 25th Jubilee, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 9a)
  - Local 3, Charter Presentation to Consolidated Bakers Union, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Local 3, First Annual Dance and Cake Exhibit, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Local 3, Diamond Jubilee, 75th Anniversary 2nd Annual Dance and Cake Show, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Local 3, Third Annual Dance and Trade Exhibit, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Local 3, Fourth Annual Entertainment and Dance, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Local 3 Tenth Anniversary Banquet, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Local 3, 13th Anniversary, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Local 3, 15th Anniversary Celebration In Memoriam to Frank Dutto, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Local 3, Merger Celebration Honoring Retiring Secretary-Treasurer Adolf Wohst, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Local 3, Fifth Anniversary Merger Celebration, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Local 22 50th Anniversary, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    Materials in Czech and English.
  - Local 51, Victory Banquet in honor of the 60th Birthday of President Harris Horowitz, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Local 51 30th Anniversary, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Local 51 35th Anniversary and 65th Birthday of President Ehrlich, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Local 51 Ehrlich Golden Wedding Anniversary, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Local 51 and Local 3 Merger Celebration, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Local 87 First Annual Dance, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Local 87 5th Anniversary Banquet and Dance, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Local 164 Mask and Civic Ball, 1930 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Local 164 Golden Anniversary Costume and Civic Ball, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Local 164 5th Anniversary Merger, Locals 507 and 164, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Local 164 10th Anniversary and Testimonial Dinner, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Local 164 Costume and Civic Ball, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Local 505 Jubilee Celebration of Former Locals 163 and 100, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Joint Executive Board 50th Anniversary, Dec 13, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - BCWIUA "Our Golden Jubilee" Locals 1, 17, 1, 50, 87, 108, 144, 164, 256, Feb 1, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - BC&TWIU 100 Years Souvenir Program, May 10, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - One Hundred Years: The Condensed History of the BC&TWIU, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - BCT: John DeConcini Retirement Dinner, Sep 26, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Local Union Reunification Committee (LURC) Testimonial Luncheon, Aug 29, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Associated Retail Bakers of Queens, Nassau, Suffolk and Affiliates Inc., Nov 12, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Associated Retail Bakers of NY 45th Annual Dinner, Nov 13, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Associated Specialty Bakery Owners of Greater New York, 1993 (Item 36)
  - Specialty Bakery Owners of America 43rd Anniversary Banquet, Jan 7, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Specialty Bakery Owners of America 47th Anniversary Banquet, Jun 3, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Specialty Bakery Owners of America 50th Anniversary Banquet, Jun 20, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Specialty Bakery Owners of America Harrison Testimonial Dinner, Jun 19, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Associated Specialty Bakery Owners of Greater New York, Mar 7, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- Series IX: Photographs and Ephemera, 1950-1990s
  Arrangement
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist.
  - Box 27, 1950s-1960s
  - Box 28, 1960s, 1978
  - Box 29, 1950s-1960s, 1966-1969
    Contains photographs used in the publication Local 3 News as well as certificates, Local 3 graphics, and Fred Wright cartoons.
  - Box 30, 1971-1980
  - Box 31, undated
    Materials related to the civil rights movement, Horn and Hardart organizing, Local 3 Ladies Auxiliary, and work site photographs.
  - Box 32, 1988-1992
    Contains photographs of membership, shop and Executive Board meetings, elections, press conferences, special events such as Christmas and charity parties, as well as negotiations and conferences.
  - Box 33, 1992-1994
    Contains photographs of general membership and Executive Board meetings, elections, special events such as luncheons and the Labor Day Parade, as well as negotiations and contract ratifications.
  - Box 34, circa 1992-1994
    Contains unidentified photographs of meetings and events, as well as three plaques honoring Local 3 President Harry Lorber, Secretary-Treasurer Harry Rubenstein and the Local 3 welfare program.
  - Box 35, Civil Rights Exhibit, 1957-1975 (Box 35, Folder 1-6)
  - Photographs and Graphics, Undated (Box 37, Box 38)